<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PCarsTA</string>
    <string name="main_activity_title">Project CARS Time Attack</string>
    <string name="edit_database_activity_title">Project CARS TimeAttack - Edit
        database</string>
    <string name="settings_activity_title">Project CARS Time Attack - Settings</string>
    <string name="waiting_car_info">Waiting for car/track information. Continue
        playing&#8230;</string>
    <string name="waiting_car_info_long">Waiting for car/track. Laptime saved
        for later processing. Continue playing&#8230;</string>
    <string name="lite_version">Free version is limited to 5 car/track entries in the database
        .</string>
    <string name="db_locked">Database can not be edited now. Exit to game\'s main menu.</string>
    <string name="settings_locked">Settings can\'t not be accessed now. Exit to game\'s main menu
        .</string>
    <string name="empty_list_view_description">Empty list view background image</string>
    <string name="restore_warning">WARNING: \n\nRestoring laptimes from file will remove
        all your current laptimes in the database.\n\nAre you sure you want to continue?</string>
    <string name="backup_ok">Backup completed successfully.</string>
    <string name="backup_fail">Error: backup failed.</string>
    <string name="restore_ok">Restore completed successfully.</string>
    <string name="restore_fail">Error: restore failed.</string>

    <!-- DBActivity -->
    <string name="allow_access">Allow access to storage to be able to restore/backup laptimes.</string>

    <!-- Preferences -->
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="pref_sound_key">pref_sound_key</string>
    <string name="pref_auto_key">pref_auto_broadcast_key</string>
    <string name="pref_auto_title">Automatic network discovery</string>
    <string name="pref_auto_summary">Enable or disable automatic broadcast address discovery</string>
    <string name="pref_broadcast_key">pref_broadcast_key</string>
    <string name="pref_broadcast_title">Broadcast address</string>
    <string name="pref_broadcast_summary">Enter your network\'s broadcast address (only if
        automatic discovery doesn\'t work)</string>
    <string name="pref_default_broadcast">192.168.1.255</string>
    <string name="pref_session_gap_key">pref_session_gap</string>
    <string name="pref_session_gap_title">Maximum gap difference for chart in session tab</string>
    <string name="pref_session_gap_summary">Recommended to set bigger gap for longer
        tracks (Default: 15)</string>
    <string name="pref_session_gap_default">15</string>

    <!-- Menus -->
    <string name="about_title">About</string>
    <string
        name="about"><![CDATA[<h2>About Project CARS</h2>Project CARS is a motorsport racing simulator
        video game developed by Slightly Mad Studios and published and distributed by Bandai Namco Entertainment
        .<br><br/><b>Project CARS Time Attack</b> is a companion app that aims to enhance the single player
        experience. It compares and saves sector times, laptimes and time differences for different combinations
        of cars and tracks.</p>]]>
    </string>
    <string
        name="help"><![CDATA[<h2>Welcome to Project CARS Time Attack!</h2><p>pCARS-TA has two modes: Session and Live
        Database.<br/><br/>Session shows a list of laptimes and sectors for each lap during a single session.
        It highlights the best sectors, best laptime for the session and the all time record for the car/track
        combination.<br/><br/>Live Database mode shows a list of all the records for the different car/track
        combinations and the total number of laps for each combo. It allows you to sort the list by car, laptime or total number of laps
        driven for each car/track. It also has an option to filter the list by car class. If one
        track is selected, only laptimes for that specific track are shown (including a chart with time
        differences). Live Database updates its content in real-time.<br/><br/>Ghost mode shows sector and laptime
        differences between your current lap and your last, best or record lap, or any other record in your database in real time.</p>
        <h3>Problems running pCARS-TA?</h3>
        <p>These are a few things you could try:<br/><br/>1. Make sure your WiFi is on and connected to the same
        network as your game console.<br/><br/>2. In game options/system, select UDP frequency 5 and UDP
        <b>Protocol Project CARS 1</b>.<br/><br/>3. pCARS-TA uses your network\'s broadcast address to
        communicate with the game. You can enter it manually in settings and deactivate the auto
        mode if this automatic broadcast discovery is not working for your network.<br/><br/>4.<b>Important:</b>
        Uninstalling the app will <u>delete all your records from the database!</u> In the full version there is an
        option in the settings menu that helps you backup/restore the database to a file in the Downloads folder of
        your device. This can also be used to transfer records between Android devices.<br/><br/>5. There is an option
        in setting to delete laptimes from the database. This can not be accessed during a race session.<br/><br/>
        6. One more thing, pCARS-TA just listens to the information that the game wants to share. Sometimes the car
        and track information can take a few laps to show up. Do not worry, all your laptimes get stored in memory
        until the car/track information is available. If the app loses focus, it loses the information for the session,
        including the laps that were in memory waiting for the car/track information from the game.<br/><br/>Note about
        <b>Reset Session</b>:
        There are times when the app is not able to tell where the player is at in the game. For example, during replays or
        when jumping from practice to qualifying and into the race. In those occasions we can use the option Reset Session
        in the options menu. That will keep the track and car configuration but will reset the laptimes for the session.
        <br/><br/>Enjoy!</p>]]>
    </string>

    <!-- Spinner A in GhostFragment -->
    <string-array name="spinner_values">
        <item>LAST LAP</item>
        <item>BEST IN SESSION</item>
        <item>ALL TIME BEST</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Spinner B in GhostFragment -->
    <string name="waiting">Waiting for car/track info</string>

</resources>
